So if the front end generation is a step too far for you,
you can also just use the very
powerful API object of type repo.
Every function on the backend that you create will be
attached to the API object in the front
end.
So whenever you make a change in your backend code, it will
immediately be available in the
front end through the API object.
Look at this.
So the function sign up with password with context can be
found here in the API object.
And it has almost the exact same footprint as the backend
function except for that it
doesn't have the function context.
The function context is provided automatically by the API,
by the fetch request function.
So you only need to provide the parameters that you require
.
And whenever you change something on the backend, it will
also be seen in the API object.
Another cool thing is that we have complete integration
with React query through the
queries object.
So if you want to do an API call, for example, every time
you go back to the page, you can
just use the queries object and choose your hook that you
want.
For example, use get me with context will make sure that
you get the locked in user and all
their information every time you come back to the
application.
And you can also easily reload and all the other
capabilities of React query.
It comes out of the box and every function that you
generate on the backend will generate
automatically the hook and the API for you.
(buzzing)