All right, so that were most of the features that we
currently have in Tiberipo.
But I also wanted to tell you a little more about what's
going to come because we're
not done yet.
We're working very hard to make it something real and
something big, something huge.
And we are focused on making the best framework for
startups, basically, to create their new
ideas as soon as fast as possible with a very good
developer experience.
Because it's just usually a lot of problems that startups
are solving, that every startup
has to solve in almost the same way.
And that's why I wanted to make this framework to really
make it easier for startups to solve
all those problems once and for all.
So yeah, that's kind of the motivation behind it.
And just to say something about Web3, from the ground up, T
iberipo has been built to
support decentralized systems.
We are experimenting a lot with this.
We are doing a lot of peer-to-peer stuff.
The API is built up in a way that it will be able to also
be exposed from your own computer.
And we will provide some tutorials for that later.
It already works.
We just need to finish the kind of the authorization and
authentication layer.
Because that's kind of not ready yet, which is kind of a
big deal, you know.
But once it will be ready, which will be pretty soon, I'll
let you know and yeah.
Hope to see some people make some stuff with this.