is that you can automatically generate documentation of
your code. When you write
your code anywhere in your code base and you provide
documents, the documentation
will be generated for those functions based on the
documents. Whenever you put
a docs folder in your package, this will also end up in the
Readme. So when you
are done writing your documentation, all you need to do is
rebuild the
operation with the rebuild operation command and within a
minute your docs
will be generated and it will look something like this.
This is the best way to generate docs I think because it
really removes the
need for doing it manually and it saves you a lot of time
while keeping the docs
always up to date with your code base.