repoships with is the database integration.
We created our own database to make it as easy as possible
for you to create your new models and make an app full of
data.
We have this database user interface where you can see
all your data, where you can create new models, where you
can add updates and delete new instances.
You can view your models in different ways.
You can search your data and much more.
So if you want to create a new model in type repo, you don
't
need to create anything hard.
It's just a TypeScript interface.
And that's it.
So you just extend a model type, you let it be indexed by
type repo, and you can see it in your database.
So if I want to add something here, all I need to do is
change the type interface, and the model is ready to be
used.
Because the indexation, it's never been as easy as this to
create or alter your database models.
[BLANK_AUDIO]