show you that this form is generated with the backend code.
The form is generated based
on the backend function just by providing the right
arguments. Another cool thing is
asset upload. That's also included in type repo. If you
provide an argument that ends
with a certain suffix like image and if you provide the
right type, it will become a picture
upload in the form. You can select an image or you can take
a picture here. Let's take
a picture. I'm not going to show my camera. And after the
picture has been taken and
you start uploading, please note there is no code required
for you at the front end. At
the backend, there's also very little code required. All
you need to do is this one line
of code to process your assets and put it in the right
place. You just take it and you
process it and then you can put it wherever you want. So,
asset upload has never been
so easy.
(clicking)