is that once you start it up and when you are in the base
of your mono repo, you get the search UI like this.
You can search all your projects with the search bar and
you can select one of the apps that you made within your
mono repo to use them.
So here, for example, if we want to open up this operation,
this web interface, we can just click and you see that it
starts loading
and open it in a new tab in your browser. It didn't even
run before in your terminal because you don't need to start
up your web interface
since we started up for you in the background if you want
to.
So this way, it's very easy to basically run your apps and
look them up fast if you want to make changes across
different apps.
It's perfect for developers that work on many different
apps at the same time inside of a huge mono repo.